Prophet T.B. Joshua, speaking forth God's Word, armed with the name of Jesus Christ,
the lame walk, captives are set free and healing comes to those
who are riddled with sickness and bound by disability.
And now witness true freedom in Christ as the Prophet encounters this man.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You look strange.
Come on, you look strange
There is a strange woman inside you.
You are a man, but you are a woman.
You are a man, you are a woman.
Who are you?
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stand up!
You were being raped.
Yes!
You have the spirit of woman inside you.
Yes, Man of God.
You keep fighting this spirit.
You know you're a man, but there is a spirit - a woman that is talking through you.
Yes, that is true, Man of God.
And when you move, you walk like a woman too.
Yes, Man of God.
You don't like it but that woman keeps talking,
keeps acting, keeps looking, keeps smiling, keeps looking, if I am right?
Yes, Man of God.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You are free! Come out!
Thank You, Lord!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
He is fighting a strange spirit and that spirit,
he knows he is a man but there is a woman living inside him.
The woman would be laughing, instead of him to laugh
but it is a woman's appearance that you would see.
When he moves, you would see a woman moving.
When he smiles, the woman smiles.
He knows that he is a man but there is a woman inside that is doing everything for him.
He is free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
It is a simple thing.
It's only that you recognise that spirit.
It's a spirit.
You can be a man but you see something entering you that acts like a woman,
but you know you are a man.
But when you smile, people admire you as a woman.
But you know you are a man.
It's a spirit; it's tormenting.
You are free. How do you feel now - tell me.
I feel relieved now that I am delivered.
- You feel relieved?
- Yes.
That being that was talking to you, how do you feel?
Is it still appearing there?
I don't feel anything anymore.
You don't feel that being again?
Yes.
Sit down there, let them loosen your hair.
Can somebody help me loosening the hair?
It's part of freedom. He can go and cut it later but he must be loosed immediately.
If I am not attending to this brother here, it would be difficult for me to attend to this woman.
Why? - Evil spirit is here and
the work of evil spirit is this.
There is difference between evil spirit and the work of evil spirit.
You know that?
You know Holy Spirit gives birth to the Spirit of God.
The oil you receive, anointing oil, you receive it from the Spirit of God, from the Holy Spirit.
He gives birth.
So in the same vein, this evil spirit has his own work.
His work is this sickness and disease.
It is not possible for any prophet to leave the evil spirit and now want to heal people.
Ok, satan is sitting down here.
Satan himself is sitting and he gives birth to all those evil spirits to go and do all sorts of things.
And you are now delivering evil spirit but satan is sitting down.
Does it make sense?
Satan would not allow it.
Even if he were to allow it, he would destroy you.
Oh, my brother. You are my friend - a very handsome boy.
Thank you. I will see you, okay?
- You're from where?
- South Africa.
Okay, South Africa. Thank you.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Testimony Time
My name is Eugene Monama.
I'm from South Africa.
During last week's service, as the man of God was praying for everyone in the church,
he just came straight to me and then said that I had a spirit of a woman inside me
and that I was raped, which is true.
It all started at a very young age.
I was six by the time it started.
But then I didn't really pay much attention to it because I was very young at that time.
Until when I was 15; that is when I got my new phone.
Then I started browsing through the net and came across pornography.
But then the strange thing about it was that I was watching man to man pornography.
So it went on like that until when I was 18,
I was doing my first year by that time.
I was staying at the campus residence at that time so I had to move out.
I lied to my mum.
I told her that I was staying at the campus residence
whereas I moved out from that campus residence.
I rented a flat on campus.
When I was 18, that was when I created my Facebook account.
And then I also downloaded an application -
it's a dating site, where you interact with different men.
So I interacted with them, and then we would make some arrangements.
I met them, I slept with them.
I was the one to start the conversation.
I would just go through their Facebook accounts
and then start the conversation from there.
The type of clothes I wore - because when I was on campus, I was a different person.
When I was on campus, I wore different clothes.
I wouldn't wear this type of clothes.
I usually wore this type of clothes when I was at home.
Whenever I went to a clothing store, I would go to the ladies' department and buy female clothes.
Then again I would go to the gents' department to buy clothes
so that whenever I went home, I would be able to wear those clothes.
I was just being led on by that spirit.
So did your parents actually notice
what was happening?
No.
Immediately after that spirit of woman entered me, I started going out to clubs, drinking.
When I was on campus, I had to walk like a female, but then...
Can you explain to us, so that people can learn,
how did you use to move or smile then like as a result of that spirit of woman?
Eugene Monama
Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
That is the brother just demonstrating in a nutshell
how he used to walk and move in a feminine manner that actually attracted fellow men to him.
The man of God said during his prophetic message last week Sunday
when the brother was being delivered that he had the spirit of woman
and as a result when he laughed, he laughed like a woman,
when he walked, he walked like a woman,
and that is what he has just demonstrated.
Okay, during 2015, as I was coming back from the club, I was drunk by that time,
I bumped into a guy on my way back to the flat.
He asked if I could come with him to his flat.
And then he lured me into a group of guys; that was when I was gang-raped.
So since then, what was happening in your life
ever since you went through that terrible experience?
Ever since that rape, everything just went from bad to worse.
And how did this problem affect your education
because you told us you were in university then.
How did that affect your studies?
During that time, I couldn't cope with my schoolwork, and I was so depressed.
So one of the psychologists prescribed some depression tablets for me.
So that means this problem affected you in many diverse ways,
to the extent that the brother said it affected his studies.
You can see him actually shedding tears of joy
because you can imagine what he must have gone through at that very tender age
when he was being
possessed with that kind of spirit.
But today we are rejoicing because Jesus Christ has taken away his past.
So all this happened all through your life.
But at what point did you know about The SCOAN and you decided to come?
It was my mum who introduced me to The SCOAN.
Really, I didn't know about this church until my mum introduced me to this church.
- So your mum actually told you to come?
- Yes.
Last week Sunday we saw how you were seated amongst the congregation,
and the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua came and laid hands on you.
Can you share with us,
what was your experience on that Sunday?
I felt like that spirit was leaving me.
And we saw that after that deliverance, the man of God instructed that your hair should be loosed.
What was your feeling, your experience as that hair was being taken off?
I felt relieved, knowing that I was delivered from that spirit.
That is the brother we are
seeing on the screen of the television.
We know that when Jesus Christ delivers us, He delivers us completely and effectually.
All that lifestyle he was living in the past as a result of that spirit of woman
he was possessed of that led him to meet with men like himself or put on a funny hairstyle,
immediately that spirit was removed, we can the hair been loosed
and the brother we are seeing right here in front of us,
we can see a perfectly normal, healthy brother.
To the glory of God.
So go ahead with your testimony.
Immediately after my deliverance, he demanded my hair to be removed.
Yeah, you can see.
So that is what we are seeing.
The person we are seeing right now, we cannot see that funny hairstyle again.
So how do you feel now, looking
normal with your normal hair style?
How do you feel?
l feel relieved now.
So what are the changes you have seen or noticed in your life
ever since that deliverance last week Sunday?
Ever since the deliverance last Sunday, I deactivated my Facebook account.
I even changed my SIM card, so I'm no longer communicating with those people anymore.
{Oh! Hallelujah! Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
My advice to those, who are having the same spirit as I had, is
that in the book of Romans 2, the Bible says,
Don't copy the customs, the costumes or the behaviour of this world.
But rather you should allow God to transform you into a new person by changing the way you think.
Because I know that along the way, you are going to meet people who are going to deceive you
and tell you that you cannot change, you were born like that, which is not true.
You just have to invite God into your heart and let Him do the rest because you cannot do it on your own.
Once again, let us put our hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Eugene Monama.
I'm 25 years old. I'm from South Africa.
Thank you very much. Could
you just share your testimony with us?
I'm here to give thanks to God for using Prophet TB Joshua to deliver me from the spirit
that made me have an affection for men like myself.
Since I've been delivered, I no longer
have an affection for men like myself.
I thank God for delivering me from that spirit.
Amen, we thank God Almighty and we rejoice with you greatly.
Right now, the man of God in his usual kind gesture knows for sure
that you need to maintain your salvation and you also need something to live on.
The man of God Prophet TB Joshua alongside Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world,
said we should give you the sum of $1,000 to support you.
Eugene Receives A Gift Of 1,000 US Dollars From Prophet T. B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV Partners
I thank the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and Emmanuel TV Partners
all over the world for blessing me with this sum of $1000.
I appreciate it a lot; I didn't expect this.
May God continue to bless Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world.
We thank the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world
for supporting you with this sum of $1,000 to help you back to your country.
My advice for them is to stay with God and trust in God.
We thank the Lord Almighty for
what He has done in your life.
We pray as you go and make the Word of God the standard for your life,
your blessing, your breakthrough
will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus!